<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accounts on Simplicity - Hugo theme</title>
    <link>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accounts on Simplicity - Hugo theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 10:15:01 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
      <atom:link href="http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>What is an account?</title>
        <link>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/what-is-account/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 10:15:01 +0200</pubDate>
        <guid>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/what-is-account/</guid>
        <description>What is an account? In Ethereum, an account is an object which holds ether and possibly other metadata. It is slightly more general than the traditional concept of a financial “account” (i.e. an account on a bank or payment service). At a basic level, an account contains:
 An address: a 20-byte unique identifier. Anyone on the network can look up an account and its associated balance/metadata using this identifier.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is a wallet?</title>
        <link>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/what-is-wallet/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 10:15:01 +0200</pubDate>
        <guid>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/what-is-wallet/</guid>
        <description>What is a wallet? Public-Key Crypto (skip if you’re already familiar) If Alice wants to send ether from her own account to Bob’s account, Alice need to create a transaction request and send it out to the network for verification. Ethereum’s usage of public-key cryptography ensures that Alice can prove that she originally initiated the transaction request. Without cryptographic mechanisms, a malicious adversary Eve could simply publicly broadcast a request that looks something like “send 5 ETH from Alice’s account to Eve’s account,” and no one would be able to verify that it didn’t come from Alice.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[Tutorial] Setting up your first wallet</title>
        <link>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/setting-up-wallet/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 10:15:01 +0200</pubDate>
        <guid>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/setting-up-wallet/</guid>
        <description>Setting up your first wallet I’ve found working with MetaMask to be a user-friendly and secure way to manage my Ethereum accounts.
Install MetaMask Go to the Chrome Web Store and install the MetaMask extension.
From time to time there are other extensions named “MetaMask” that are branded similarly, which are likely to be phishing scams. You’re fine if you install the MetaMask extension that clearly has the appropriate number of downloads and ratings.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>[Tutorial] Browse account data with Etherscan</title>
        <link>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/browse-etherscan/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 10:15:01 +0200</pubDate>
        <guid>http://briangu33.github.io/learn-ethereum/accounts/browse-etherscan/</guid>
        <description>Browse Account Data with Etherscan Etherscan is a helpful web application that allows you to view information about the blockchain in a human-readable way.
The entire history of all transactions, blocks, accounts, code, and other metadata collectively make up the “blockchain,” which is stored on every single Ethereum node. Etherscan.io runs a few nodes of their own, and thus has a copy of the entire blockchain on its machines. Etherscan then surfaces all of this data in a webapp.</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
